<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<geonames style="MEDIUM">
<totalResultsCount>1</totalResultsCount>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Abstract</glossaryName>
<Description>An Abstract is a summary of your entire research report.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Active voice</glossaryName>
<Description>The active voice focuses on the person and what he or she did. E.g. "We made transcripts of all the 50 interviews that we have collected."</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>APA</glossaryName>
<Description>American Psychological Association - a commonly used citation style.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Appendices</glossaryName>
<Description>This is where you will include project planning and survey documents related to your project.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Bibliography</glossaryName>
<Description>A Bibliography lists the sources you have used in your report.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Conclusion</glossaryName>
<Description>The Conclusion provides a summary of the findings and a possible answer to the problem statement.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Discussion</glossaryName>
<Description>The impact of your findings on your research problem statement and its implications are examined in the Discussion section.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Findings</glossaryName>
<Description>The results and findings are represented using charts and graphs in the Findings section.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>First person</glossaryName>
<Description>This is a writing style describing people using words such as "I", "we" and "you". </Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Formal language style</glossaryName>
<Description>Is impersonal and uses the passive voice and avoids personal first person pronouns.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Informal language style</glossaryName>
<Description>Is personal and uses the active voice and first person pronoun.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Introduction</glossaryName>
<Description>The Introduction contains information about your report (purpose, scope, etc.) as well background information, which will familiarise readers with the subject of your research.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Literature Review</glossaryName>
<Description>A literature review is a sub-section within Introduction which describes the relevant research material that  you have read.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>MLA</glossaryName>
<Description>Modern Language Association - a commonly used citation style.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Paraphrasing</glossaryName>
<Description>This involves rewriting the information in your own words and making reference to the source  rather than 'copying and pasting' directly from the source.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Passive voice</glossaryName>
<Description>The passive voice focuses on the information and processes rather than the person who performed the tasks. E.g. "Written transcripts were made of all 50 interviews."</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Research Methods</glossaryName>
<Description>The Research Methods section contains a detailed account of how you collected your data.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Recommendations</glossaryName>
<Description>This is a sub-section within Conclusion where you suggest actions, changes or solutions to problems identified in the research. </Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Sample</glossaryName>
<Description>A sample is the subset of a population. It is randomly picked from the population.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Third person</glossaryName>
<Description>This is a writing style making indirect reference to articles and people. E.g. "It" and "The researchers".</Description>
</glossary>


</geonames>
