<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<geonames style="MEDIUM">
<totalResultsCount>1</totalResultsCount>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>Bibliography</glossaryName>
<Description>A list of resources that are referenced in your work. These should be written in a citation format.</Description>
</glossary>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>Blog</glossaryName>
<Description>An online dairy of personal notes.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Citation</glossaryName>
<Description>A reference to a resource such as a website or a book. Citations are written in a particular format such as the APA or the MLA.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Common knowledge</glossaryName>
<Description>Information that everybody knows in a community or group.</Description>
</glossary>



<glossary>
<glossaryName>Format</glossaryName>
<Description>A particular order of structure of something such as a citation.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>In-text citation </glossaryName>
<Description>A brief citation that appears in the text of your paper that allows the reader to know the source of your references. All in-text citations must be accompanied by their full citations in the bibliography.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Journal</glossaryName>
<Description>A magazine that is written around a specific subject. E.g. An archeology journal.</Description>
</glossary>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>Paraphrasing</glossaryName>
<Description>The re-writing of what somebody has said or written. When you paraphrase, remember to cite the source.</Description>
</glossary>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>Plagiarism</glossaryName>
<Description>The act of stealing somebody else’s work or ideas and passing it off as your own.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Quotation</glossaryName>
<Description>A sentence or phrase taken from somebody else’s work and reproduced as it is (without changing the words).</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Reference</glossaryName>
<Description>Mentioning or pointing out to somebody else’s work or ideas.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Source</glossaryName>
<Description>The person or thing from where you got information or ideas from.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Summarising</glossaryName>
<Description>To re-write a long article or a book in a shorter format.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Techniques</glossaryName>
<Description>A particular way of doing a task or activity. E.g. the technique of rowing a boat, or writing a research paper.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Wikipedia</glossaryName>
<Description>A free online encyclopedia available at http://www.wikipedia.com/</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Youtube</glossaryName>
<Description>A video-sharing website available at http://www.youtube.com/</Description>
</glossary>

</geonames>
