<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<sets>
  <set id="1">
    <questions>
      <question id="1">
        <text>Refer to the cheat sheet poster on the topic of 'Poverty'.\n\nVisit this website <![CDATA[ <u><a href="http://www.nlb.gov.sg/sure/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/CheatSheetPoverty.pdf">http://www.nlb.gov.sg/sure/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/CheatSheetPoverty.pdf</a></u> ]]>.\n\nThe cheat sheet is an educational poster. It provides you with an overview of the topic ‘poverty’. In addition, you can also refer to the list of references provided. Assuming that you want to search for this poster using a search engine, choose the most accurate search strategy from the options provided below:</text>
        <options>
          <option id="1" ans="true">SURE poverty cheat sheet</option>
          <option id="2" ans="false">Poverty</option>
          <option id="3" ans="false">SURE</option>
        </options>
		<image></image>
      </question>
	  <question id="2">
        <text>Refer to the infographics on the topic of ‘How to Paraphrase’.\n\nVisit this website <![CDATA[ <u><a href="http://www.nlb.gov.sg/sure/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Infographic-how-to-paraphrase.pdf">http://www.nlb.gov.sg/sure/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Infographic-how-to-paraphrase.pdf</a></u> ]]>.\n\nAn infographic is a visual representation of information or data, and usually appears in the form of a chart or diagram. This infographic provides you with an overview of paraphrasing, or how to express the meaning of texts using different words for more clarity. If you were to search for this infographic using a search engine, what would be the most accurate search strategy from the options provided below?</text>
        <options>
          <option id="1" ans="false">how to paraphrase</option>
          <option id="2" ans="true">SURE infographic paraphrase</option>
          <option id="3" ans="false">paraphrasing techniques</option>
        </options>
		<image></image>
      </question>
	  <question id="3">
        <text>Refer to the video on the theme ‘How to spot a fake website’.\n\nVisit this website <![CDATA[ <u><a href="http://www.nlb.gov.sg/sure/video-case-of-the-antique-chairs">http://www.nlb.gov.sg/sure/video-case-of-the-antique-chairs</a></u> ]]>.\n\nVideos provide another channel for learning through moving images. This video shares with you the 5-finger test for evaluating information and spotting a fake website. Assuming that you want to search for this video using a search engine, choose the most accurate search strategy from the options provided below:</text>
        <options>
          <option id="1" ans="false">fake website video</option>
          <option id="2" ans="false">spotting fake website video</option>
          <option id="3" ans="true">video fake website nlb</option>
        </options>
		<image></image>
      </question>
	  <question id="4">
        <text>Refer to the article on ‘Do fishes sleep?’.\n\nVisit this website <![CDATA[ <u><a href="http://www.nlb.gov.sg/sure/do-fishes-sleep">http://www.nlb.gov.sg/sure/do-fishes-sleep</a></u> ]]>.\n\nThe S.U.R.E portal contains many interesting articles that will enhance your general knowledge. This article answers the interesting question of whether fishes sleep. If you were to search for this article using a search engine, what would be the most accurate search strategy from the options provided below?</text>
        <options>
          <option id="1" ans="false">do fishes sleep</option>
          <option id="2" ans="false">how fishes sleep</option>
          <option id="3" ans="true">fishes sleep site:.nlb.gov.sg/sure</option>
        </options>
		<image></image>
      </question>
    </questions>
  </set>
</sets>