<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<geonames style="MEDIUM">
<totalResultsCount>1</totalResultsCount>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Boxout</glossaryName>
<Description>A part of the page in the newspaper that is shaded in a different colour.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Broadsheet</glossaryName>
<Description>Newspaper that focuses on unbiased, direct reporting of facts and current affairs information using serious and objective language.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Byline</glossaryName>
<Description>A part of a newspaper page that has the name of the reporter.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Cut</glossaryName>
<Description>Photo or graphic in a newspaper.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Cutline</glossaryName>
<Description>Line describing a picture that accompanies a story or article in the newspaper. This is also called caption.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Editorials</glossaryName>
<Description>Newspaper articles in which editorial team expresses their viewpoint(s) on an important issue. This is typical of broadsheets.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Feature articles</glossaryName>
<Description>Newspaper articles that analyses the background and issues related to a wide range of topics (e.g. business, politics).</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>General-interest newspaper</glossaryName>
<Description>General-interest newspapers are usually journals of current news These can include political events, crime, business, culture, sports, and opinions (ie editorials, columns, or political cartoons).</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Headline</glossaryName>
<Description>Main words or statements of the newspaper article often written in large bold font to grab the attention of the reader.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Index</glossaryName>
<Description>Table of selected contents of articles in the newspaper providing page numbers.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Inverted Pyramid</glossaryName>
<Description>Method of writing usually used in newspapers where parts of a story are placed in descending order of importance.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Lead</glossaryName>
<Description>Summary of a newspaper story containing answers to 2 or more of the 5W and 1H questions (what, who, when, where, why and how). This is sometimes shown in bold.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Masthead</glossaryName>
<Description>Title block or logo identifying the newspaper at the top of the front-page.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Microfilm</glossaryName>
<Description>A storage medium for archiving previous or back issues of newspapers which can be read using a microfilm reader.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Podcasts</glossaryName>
<Description>Multimedia files (e.g. short audio, often video clips) posted on the Internet for download by users. Podcasts of news stories are becoming increasingly available by news providers.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>RSS Feeds</glossaryName>
<Description>RSS or Really Simple Syndication are customised news alerts sent to an email account to be read using a news reader (e.g. Bloglines).</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Secondary Lead</glossaryName>
<Description>A picture with a headline which gives a sneak preview of a story that you might find inside the newspaper.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Special-interest newspaper</glossaryName>
<Description>This newspaper is topical in nature and has a targeted reader-base. It targets specific communities such as people interest in the arts, sports or a certain lifestyle.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Strapline</glossaryName>
<Description>This is a sub-headline below the main headline providing additional information about the news article.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Tabloid</glossaryName>
<Description>Newspaper that focuses on sensational reporting using subjective and emotional language.</Description>
</glossary>

</geonames>
