<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<geonames style="MEDIUM">
<totalResultsCount>1</totalResultsCount>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Bibliography</glossaryName>
<Description>A list that is added at the end of the project report to indicate the resources that have been referred to.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Big 6™ Model</glossaryName>
<Description>The most widely known and used learning model, developed by educators, Mike Eisenberg and Bob Berkowitz, to impart information and technology skills.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Boolean operators</glossaryName>
<Description>The three Boolean operators defined by George Boole. The operator AND is used to narrow down the search by combining two or more keywords, operator OR is used to expand the search by using alternative keywords while operator NOT is used to eliminate a concept or keyword that is irrelevant, yet closely related to the main idea.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Citation</glossaryName>
<Description>The act of referencing to the original work using styles such as Modern Language Association (MLA) and American Psychological Association (APA).</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Communications (media) literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>The ability to learn from the media.</Description>
</glossary>
<!--
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Critique literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>The ability to evaluate both print and electronic resources using a set of criteria and understand the dangers of plagiarism.</Description>
</glossary>
-->

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Digital and network literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>The ability to access different types of Web content on the Internet.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Empowering 8 Model</glossaryName>
<Description>Learning model developed by the International Federation of Library Associations and Institutions, Action for Development through Libraries Programme (IFLA-ALP) and the National Institute of Library and Information Sciences (NILIS) of Sri Lanka to create awareness of information skills for learning.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Evaluate</glossaryName>
<Description>To judge the value or condition of (someone or something) in a careful and thoughtful way.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Information literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>A life skill, critical to survive and flourish in society today and in the future. It consists of the ability to identify, locate, evaluate and use information efficiently and effectively.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Knowledge economy</glossaryName>
<Description>The economy of the 21st century that is information-driven, and which calls for information literacy rather than computer literacy.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Libguide</glossaryName>
<Description>The libguide is a collection of resource guides and bibliography compiled by librarians to help you in your research on various topics.</Description>
</glossary>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>NLB's IL Model</glossaryName>
<Description>Learning model developed by NLB Singapore to implement Project Work at the school level.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>NLB's IL Programme</glossaryName>
<Description>NLB's programme that has been designed in partnership with educators and librarians to educate the public, including students, on how to search, retrieve and use the information.</Description>
</glossary>
<!--
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Pathfinder</glossaryName>
<Description>A list of useful books, Internet resources and useful databases available in the library to be used as an introductory tool for students to search for information on the subject.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Publishing literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>The ability to present and communicate research information using appropriate techniques.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Research literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>The ability to undertake simple research by designing survey instruments, such as questionnaires and interviews and to synthesise information from different sources.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Resource literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>The ability to use printed materials and electronic information resources effectively.</Description>
</glossary>
-->

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Research</glossaryName>
<Description>The systematic investigation into and study of materials and sources in order to establish facts and reach new conclusion.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Source</glossaryName>
<Description>A place, person or thing from which something originates or can be obtained.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Technology (computer) literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>The ability to use computer applications.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Understand</glossaryName>
<Description>Know the meaning.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Visual literacy</glossaryName>
<Description>The ability to learn through visuals.</Description>
</glossary>

</geonames>