<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<geonames style="MEDIUM">
<totalResultsCount>1</totalResultsCount>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Activity</glossaryName>
<Description>A group of tasks is an activity. For example, planning research is an activity which has many tasks.</Description>
</glossary>
		
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Affinity diagramming</glossaryName>
<Description>Affinity diagramming is a technique for grouping related items (found during the research) together.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Concept mapping</glossaryName>
<Description>Concept mapping is a technique for visualising the relationships among different concepts uncovered during the research process.</Description></glossary>
	
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Interview</glossaryName>
<Description>A research method to understand and empathise with subjects on a research topic by asking questions.</Description>
</glossary>
	
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Literature review</glossaryName>
<Description>A comprehensive survey of publications in a specific field of study or related to a particular line of research.</Description>
</glossary>
	
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Open-ended</glossaryName>
<Description>A topic is open-ended when it is too broad or needs more focus to make it a viable research topic. The following is a open-ended research topic: Journeys</Description>
</glossary>
	
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Primary sources</glossaryName>
<Description>Primary sources are those that are original and  uninterpreted and created during the time of the event in question.</Description>
</glossary>
		
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Problem Statement</glossaryName>
<Description>A statement posed as a problem that directs the research effort. A research topic can be a problem statement.</Description>
</glossary>

	
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Quantitative research</glossaryName>
<Description>Research that deals with hard data or statistics.</Description>
</glossary>
		
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Qualitative research</glossaryName>
<Description>Research that deals with soft data or observations, interpretations or meanings.</Description>
</glossary>
	
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Research</glossaryName>
<Description>Systematic study to understand a phenomenon or uncover new ideas and insights.</Description>
</glossary>
		
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Research Topic</glossaryName>
<Description>The statement or question that directs the research effort. For example, Impact of Haze on Singapore Economy.</Description>
</glossary>
		
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Survey</glossaryName>
<Description>A research method to collect participant responses on facts, opinions usually through questionnaires.</Description>
</glossary>
		
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Secondary sources</glossaryName>
<Description>Secondary sources are those that have summarised, interpreted or analysed existing sources. In other words, secondary sources are based on primary sources.</Description>
</glossary>
	
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Timeline</glossaryName>
<Description>A timeline is a diagram that shows how one variable is organised by time. Project activities on the X-axis vs. weeks it is going to take to complete them on the Y-axis is a timeline.</Description>
</glossary>
	
<glossary>
<glossaryName>Well-defined</glossaryName>
<Description>A topic is well-defined when the focus is narrow and it is understood. For example, the following research topic is well-defined: What are the practical ways to go green at home?</Description>
</glossary>

</geonames>
