<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<geonames style="MEDIUM">
<totalResultsCount>1</totalResultsCount>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>APA</glossaryName>
<Description>Citation technique developed by the American Psychological Association (APA)  for subjects in the social sciences.</Description>
</glossary>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>Citation</glossaryName>
<Description>A citation is the direct reference to a source used. This can be done in the text called 'in-text citation' where information such as the author's last name, year of publication and page numbers in some instances is provided. A reference list is made up of a number of citations.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>MLA</glossaryName>
<Description>Citation technique developed by the Modern Language Association (MLA) for subjects in the humanities.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Note-taking</glossaryName>
<Description>Involves recording the main points of information that is relevant to you after scanning.</Description>
</glossary>



<glossary>
<glossaryName>Paraphrasing</glossaryName>
<Description>Involves re-writing information extracted from other sources in your own words.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Plagiarism</glossaryName>
<Description>Plagiarism is an act of literary theft, where one passes off the ideas or words of other as one's own, without crediting the source.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Reference List</glossaryName>
<Description>A collection of resources used in the report. This includes printed and electronic resources such as books, journals, CD-ROMs, the Internet, online databases. A Reference List is also known as a bibliography.</Description>
</glossary>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>Scanning</glossaryName>
<Description>Involves reading through a relevant document very quickly to look for specific information or facts.</Description>
</glossary>


<glossary>
<glossaryName>Skimming</glossaryName>
<Description>A quick read of the document to determine the gist or essence of the contents.</Description>
</glossary>

</geonames>
