<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<geonames style="MEDIUM">
<totalResultsCount>1</totalResultsCount>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Abstract</glossaryName>
<Description>An abstract is a summary of your research report.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Appendix</glossaryName>
<Description>This is a section of your report where you would insert documents that provide more information about your research and findings. This includes project planning and survey documents.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Attention grabber</glossaryName>
<Description>Attention grabbers are used, usually at the beginning of a presentation, to capture the audience's interest and attention. This could take different forms, such as a shocking statement, a story or an interesting prop.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Bibliography</glossaryName>
<Description>A bibliography lists the sources that you have referred to in your report. The bibliography is usually placed at the end of your project report.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Blog</glossaryName>
<Description>A blog is a website that contains an online journal with reflections, comments, and often hyperlinks provided by the writer(s).</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Concept map</glossaryName>
<Description>A concept map is a visual organiser that helps you to think up new and related ideas from one or multiple concepts.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Conclusion</glossaryName>
<Description>The conclusion provides a summary of the major inferences made from the findings, an answer to the problem statement and your recommendations.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Discussion</glossaryName>
<Description>This section analyses the impact of the research findings on your problem statement. A comparison may also be made with previous research done by other researchers.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Findings</glossaryName>
<Description>The research results are summarised and presented in the Findings section.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Introduction</glossaryName>
<Description>The introduction states the purpose and scope of your research. It also provides useful background information that will familiarise the readers with the research topic and why it was chosen.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>New Media</glossaryName>
<Description>New Media refers to the technology that allows people to communicate, interact and share information conveniently with each other through the Internet.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Oral presentation techniques</glossaryName>
<Description>These are tips that will help you improve your oral presentations. They include tips on: [br][ul][li]Pronunciation[/li] [li]Pace/tone[/li] [li]Projection[/li] [li]Pause fillers[/li] [li] Posture and gestures[/li][/ul]</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Pause fillers</glossaryName>
<Description>These are words or sounds that are spoken to fill up gaps in speech (e.g. "ah..." or "erm...").</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Podcast</glossaryName>
<Description>A podcast is a set of pre-recorded audio files that is distributed over the Internet. It can be downloaded for playback on media devices or computers.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Presentation tools</glossaryName>
<Description>These are audio or visual tools used to enhance your presentation. They include PowerPoint slides, charts, and audio or video clips.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Q&amp;A session</glossaryName>
<Description>This is the part of the presentation when the audience and teacher pose questions to the project team to find out more about their project.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Research Methods</glossaryName>
<Description>The Research Methods section contains a detailed explanation of the primary research method used, how you carried it out and the people you surveyed or interviewed.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Rhetorical question</glossaryName>
<Description>A question to which no answer is expected.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Transitions</glossaryName>
<Description>These are points or links to indicate a change to the next topic in the presentation.</Description>
</glossary>

<glossary>
<glossaryName>Vodcast</glossaryName>
<Description>A vodcast is video content that is distributed over the Internet.</Description>
</glossary>

</geonames>
